ARNOLD REDOBLADO FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

663 Caboto Trail Markham, ON L3R 5V8 T 905.479.0725 M 647.407.5270 arnold.redoblado@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arnoldredoblado arnoldredoblado.com

PROFILE

I'm Arn and I put together my first computer as an 11 year old and haven't stopped since. I have 18 years of industry experience built on skills in product support, application development and project management. I am a team player and a team builder. What's next for me? Transitioning my career to web design, development and creating applications.

EXPERIENCE

IMS Health (Previously Cegedim/Dendrite/Synavant): 1998 - 2016

A global information and technology services company providing clients in the healthcare industry with end-to-end solutions to measure and improve their performance.

Marketing Services Tech & Infrastructure Support Specialist: 2011 - 2016

Responsible for management of marketing requests and content deliveries to clients in the pharmaceutical industry, managing database and technical requests, customer expectations and workflow. Created application and database queries to fulfill client requests for targeted mailing, email and fax campaigns. Application development including quality assurance and success metrics reporting and streamlining/refactoring internal processes to improve efficiency and reduce processing time.

Programmer Analyst: 2008 - 2011

Responsible for maintaining and supporting proprietary mobile customer relationship management solution for two major pharmaceutical companies, Abbot and Basilea. The role included requirements gathering, testing and implementation to production for tasks such as territory alignments and deployment of new modules and features (ex. inventory tracking and email notifications.)

EDUCATION

Bitmaker 2016

9 week immersive course in web development

Seneca College 2008-2012

Computer Programming diploma

WHAT DO I BRING TO WORK EACH DAY? Communication Skills Technical Skills Talent for teamwork Problem-solving Skills My lunch SKILLS SQL RUBY HTML/CSS SWIFT

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST